let savollar12 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "alone",
        answer: "A. yolg'iz",
        options: [
            "A. yolg'iz",
            "B. birga",
            "C. hamroh",
            "D. samimiy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "apartment",
        answer: "B. kvartira",
        options: [
            "A. uy",
            "B. kvartira",
            "C. xona",
            "D. ofis"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "article",
        answer: "C. maqola",
        options: [
            "A. kitob",
            "B. yozuv",
            "C. maqola",
            "D. eylon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "artist",
        answer: "D. rassom",
        options: [
            "A. yozuvchi",
            "B. musiqachi",
            "C. raqqos",
            "D. rassom"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "attitude",
        answer: "A. munosabat",
        options: [
            "A. munosabat",
            "B. xatti-harakat",
            "C. ko'rinish",
            "D. kayfiyat"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "to compare",
        answer: "B. taqqoslamoq",
        options: [
            "A. ajratish",
            "B. taqqoslamoq",
            "C. baholash",
            "D. qaror qabul qilish"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to judge",
        answer: "C. baho bermoq",
        options: [
            "A. eytiborsiz qoldirish",
            "B. oldini olish",
            "C. baho bermoq",
            "D. qadrlash"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "magazine",
        answer: "A. jurnal",
        options: [
            "A. jurnal",
            "B. gazeta",
            "C. kitob",
            "D. buklet"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "material",
        answer: "D. material",
        options: [
            "A. asbob",
            "B. mashina",
            "C. jihoz",
            "D. material"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "meal",
        answer: "B. ovqatlanish vaqti",
        options: [
            "A. taom",
            "B. ovqatlanish vaqti",
            "C. yengil ovqat",
            "D. ichimlik"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "method",
        answer: "A. usul",
        options: [
            "A. usul",
            "B. muammo",
            "C. reja",
            "D. g'oya"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "neighbor",
        answer: "B. qo'shni",
        options: [
            "A. do'st",
            "B. qo'shni",
            "C. hamkasb",
            "D. qarindosh"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "professional",
        answer: "C. kasbiy",
        options: [
            "A. havaskor",
            "B. talaba",
            "C. kasbiy",
            "D. boshlovchi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "profit",
        answer: "D. foyda",
        options: [
            "A. zarar",
            "B. xarajat",
            "C. qarz",
            "D. foyda"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "quality",
        answer: "B. sifat",
        options: [
            "A. miqdor",
            "B. sifat",
            "C. narx",
            "D. uslub"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "shape",
        answer: "A. shakl",
        options: [
            "A. shakl",
            "B. rang",
            "C. o'lcham",
            "D. tuzilish"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "space",
        answer: "D. bo'sh joy",
        options: [
            "A. obyekt",
            "B. mebel",
            "C. rasm",
            "D. bo'sh joy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "stair",
        answer: "B. zina",
        options: [
            "A. eshik",
            "B. zina",
            "C. deraza",
            "D. balkon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "symbol",
        answer: "C. ramz",
        options: [
            "A. ism",
            "B. harf",
            "C. ramz",
            "D. raqam"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "thin",
        answer: "A. ozg'in",
        options: [
            "A. ozg'in",
            "B. semiz",
            "C. keng",
            "D. tor"
        ]
    }
];
